School of Engineering and Applied Science Records, 1884-2017: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Dean of the School of Engineering and Applied Science, 1896-2016 September 13; 149.37 linear feet 121 boxes Digital Folders: 97, Digital Files: 2,135 73,438 email messages
  - Subseries 1B: Joseph C. Elgin, 1922-1972; 97.92 linear feet 79 boxes
    - Engineering 425, 1953-1959; 24 folders
      - Spring Term, 1953-1958; 11 folders
        - Enrollment, 1957; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 16)
        - Enrollment, 1956; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 17)
        - 1954, 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 18)
        - Course Material, 1954; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 19)
        - Enrollment, 1955; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 20)
        - Course Material, 1955; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 21)
        - Enrollment, 1953; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 22)
        - Course Material, 1956; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 23)
      - Fall Term, 1953-1957; 9 folders
        - Course Material, 1957; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 24)
        - Enrollment, 1957; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 25)
        - Enrollment, 1956; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 26)
        - Course Material, 1956; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 27)
        - Course Material, 1955; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 28)
        - Enrollment, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 29)
        - Enrollment, 1954; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 30)
        - Enrollment, 1953; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 31)
        - Course Material, 1953; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 32)
      - Precept, 1953-1959; 4 folders
        - Wilcox Textile Machinery Company, 1953; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 33)
        - R. H. Nowell Company, 1959; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 34)
        - William B. Gunniston Company, 1955; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 35)
        - Bramer Restaurant Company, 1957; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Engineering 434, Spring Term, 1956-1960; more than 3 folders
      - Enrollment, 1957-1960; 4 folders (Box 70, Folder 37 to 40)
      - Course Material, 1957-1958; 3 folders (Box 70, Folder 41 to 43)
      - Course Schedule, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 44)
    - Engineering 526, Spring Term, 1955; 2 folders
      - Enrollment, 1955; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 45)
      - Course Material, 1955; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 46)
    - Mechanical Engineering 526, Spring Term, 1954-1956; 2 folders (Box 70, Folder 47 to 48)
    - Engineering 425, 1934-1958; 20 folders
      - Baltimore Lithographing Company, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Engineering 425 Precept, 1934-1958; 18 folders
        - Advance Aircraft Company, 1950; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 2)
        - Pembroke Electric Company, 1957; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 3)
        - Rayburn Machinery Company, 1958; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 4)
        - Chapman Gear Company, 1936; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 5)
        - Cluett, Peabody and Company Incorporated, 1936-1937; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 6)
        - Layout, 1945; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 7)
        - Lawlock Beverage Company, 1934-1937; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 8)
        - Miller Cabinet Company, 1955; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 9)
        - Nelson Manufacturing Company, 1956; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 10)
        - Owl Wire Company, 1958; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 11)
        - Peale Manufacturing Company, 1947; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 12)
        - Pepsi-Cola Company, 1948; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 13)
        - UVX Industries, Incorporated, 1950; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 14)
        - Mr. White, Grocer, 1954; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 15)
        - General Motors Corp. I-II, 191934, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 16)
        - Burrill Company Incorporated, 1936; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 17)
        - Chrysler Corporation, 1936; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 18)
        - Wrenn Homes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - References, 1947-1949; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Report on Streamline, Light-Weight, High-Speed Passenger Trains, 1948-1950; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - "Proceedings of The Graduate Council of Princeton University", 1951 November 16; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Class of 1936 Blank Letterheads, undated, 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Daily Princetonian, 1957 February 14; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Bicentennial Conference Notes, 1946; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Minutes of Faculty Meetings, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Ford Foundation Fellowships, 1962; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Graduate Fellowships and Scholarships, Nominations for, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - 400-Numbered Course, Graduate School Catalogue, 1959; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Independent Work, 1958-1964; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - Princeton University - Junior College Transfer Plan, 1962-1967; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Alexander Keer, 1957; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - Executive Committee, 1966-1969; 5 folders
      - Active, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 33)
      - Minutes, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 34)
      - Minutes, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 35)
      - Active, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 36)
      - Minutes, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - Course Proposals and Changes, 1962-1970; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Course Descriptions - Student Use, 1951; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Course of Study Committee, 1947-1957; 1963-1969; 2 folders (Box 72, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Crocco, Luigi, 1948-1971; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Curriculum Committee Report, 1955; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Contributors to Engineering School, 1956-1959; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Contributor - American Instititute of Electrical Engineers, Philadelphia Women's Auxiliary, 1957; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Coordinating Committee on Control of Engineering Processes, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Remarks to Corporate Advisers, 1954 November; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Cooper Union Presidential Installation, 1962; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Cooper Union Centennial, 1959; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Cornell University - The Program on Science, Technology and Society, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Corporate Associates, 1954-1956; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Daniels, W. B, 1964-1968; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Dartmouth College, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Davione, Doctor F, 1969; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Departmental Chairmen - Memos, 1966-1971; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Determination of Academic Standing, 1968-1971; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Corporate Gifts Committee, Minutes, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - De Wiest, J. M. R, 1962 August 29; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Denning, Peter J, 1968-1972; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Di Pace, Joseph Anthony, 1956-1958; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Dodge, Barnett F, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Doolittle, Arthur K, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Dreyfus, Doctor Camille - Celanese Corporation, 1948-1956; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - DuPont De Nemours and Company, 1955-1960; 2 folders
      - 1957-1960, 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 27)
      - 1955-1957, 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - 'D' Miscellaneous, 1954-1963; portions of 2 boxes
      - 1962-1963, 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 29)
      - 1959-1962, 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 30)
      - 1959-1960, 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 31)
      - 1958-1959, 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 32)
      - 1957-1958, 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 33)
      - 1957-1962, 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 34)
      - 1954-1956, 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Education Testing Service, 1954-1962; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Educational Program, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Education and World Affairs, 1968; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Electrical Engineering Department, 1944-1971; 9 folders
      - 1965-1971, 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - 1958-1962, 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - 1948-1953, 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - 1954-1958, 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - 1944-1950, 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Minutes, 1946-1952; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Current Faculty Minutes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Graduate Students, 1948; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - 1950-1951, 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Elgin, J. C, 1943-1950; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Emmons, Howard W, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Engineering Building, 1928; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Engineering Corporation Fund Ideas, 1954; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Engineering Council, 1954-1959; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Engineering Education, 1961; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Engineering and Scientific Education - Foundation of National Strength Conference, 1957; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Engineering Plus, 1926; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Engineering at Princeton, 1952-1958; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Engineers Council for Professional Development, 1941-1959; 4 folders
      - 1954-1958, 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 23)
      - 1941-1959, 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - Inspection, 1955 January 17-18; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 25)
      - Inspection Material Supplied, 1955; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Engineering Brochures, 1952-1954; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Engineers Council for Professional Development, 1936-1952; 4 folders
      - 1945-1949, 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - 1936-1945, 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Regional Chairman, 1948; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - 1951-1952, 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Engineering Graduates, 1926-1939; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Engineers Joint Council, 1946-1970; 5 folders
      - 1959-1960, 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - 1946-1950, 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - 1956-1957, 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - 1954-1955, 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Engineering Manpower Commission, 1965-1970; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Engineering Mechanics Committee - Reports, 1956; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Engineering Physics, 1954; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Engineering Sciences Committee, circa 1946; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Engineering Ad Hoc Computer Committee, 1965-1970; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Engineering Central Shop, 1965-1971; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Engineering School Budget, 1928-1955; 3 folders
      - Approved, 1953; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 16)
      - 1952-1955, 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 17)
      - 1928-1949, 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Engineering Curriculum, Ad Hoc Faculty Committee, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Engineering School - Degree Requirements, Ad Hoc Committee to Restudy, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Engineering School Committees, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Engineers Joint Council, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Examinations and Standing Committee Actions, 1954-1960; 3 folders
      - 1955-1958, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - 1954-1955, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - 1955-1960, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - 'E' Miscellaneous, 1953-1963; 8 folders
      - 1962-1963, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - 1960-1962, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - 1958-1960, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - 1959, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - 1957-1958, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - 1956-1957, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - 1955-1956, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - 1953-1955, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Alumni Programs Office, 1958-1959; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Clerk, 1957-1959; 1959-1962; 2 folders (Box 75, Folder 14 to 15)
    - Brookhaven National Laboratory Report, Lecture Series, 1962; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Charles Kettering Foundation Annual Report, 1961; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1922-1954; 4 folders
      - 1922-1940, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - 1941-1948, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - 1945-1946, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - 1949-1954, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1940-1970; more than 4 folders
      - Aerospace and Mechanical Engineering, 1940-1970; 3 folders (Box 77, Folder 1 to 3)
      - Chemical Engineering, 1951-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Civil and Geological Engineering, 1946-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Electrical Engineering, 1948-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Graphics, Research Appointments, Correspondence, 1942-1966; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Rice, Richard A.- Visiting Lecturer, Civil Engineering, 1964-1967; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Sellery, Robert A., Junior, 1966-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Harbour, Peter J, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Heitzman, Edward J, 1966-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Tauchert, Theodore R, 1964-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Brush, Lucien M. Jr, 1963-1969; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Kinsman, David J, 1965-1967; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Kissam, Philip, 1957-1965; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Richards, Rowland Jr, 1964-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Tschebotarioff, Gregory P, 1946-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Altman, Stanley M, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Edward G. Coffman, 1966-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Davisson, Lee D, 1964-1970; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Peter Weiner, 1966-1969; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Faculty Salary Review, 1940-1970; 6 folders
      - 1943-1969, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 22)
      - 1952-1970, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 23)
      - 1940-1970, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 24)
      - 1951-1970, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 25)
      - 1946-1970, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 26)
      - 1948-1970, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Research Appointments, 1941-1963; more than 8 folders
      - Plastics, 1948-1963; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Electrical Engineering, 1941-1963; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Civil Engineering, 1945-1962; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Mechanical Engineering, 1944-1963; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Graphics, 1944-1962; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Geological Engineering, 1945-1963; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Chemical Engineering, 1947-1963; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Aeronautical Engineering, 1949-1963; 2 folders (Box 78, Folder 8 to 9)
    - Conversion of Group Grades, 1960-1964; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Manning Plans, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Faculty - Memos to Executive Committee, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Memos, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Feiss, Julian W, 1963-1970; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Fellowships - Wallace and Lonthrop, 1965-1971; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Foundation for Instrumentation Education and Research Incorporated - Lloyd E. Slater, Executive Director, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Field Lectureships, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Forrestal Research Center, 1958; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Freshman Parents Day, 1965-1970; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Freshmen Week, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Freshmen (Special Program for Entering Engineering Freshmen, Disadvantaged), 1969; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Freshman Year Committee, 1962-1970; 1957-1960; 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 13 to 14)
    - Freshman Advisers, 1956; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Freshmen Class of 1951 - Lists, Correspondence, Etc., 1947, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Freshmen Lists, 1945; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - 'F' Miscellaneous, 1955-1963; 6 folders
      - 1962-1963, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 18)
      - 1960, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 19)
      - 1959, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 20)
      - 1959-1960, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 21)
      - 1955-1958, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 22)
      - 1955-1956, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Gemmell, Edgar M, 1954-1962; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - General Electric Company, 1955-1962; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Geological Engineering, 1939-1966; portions of 2 boxes
      - 1958, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 26)
      - 1955-1958, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 27)
      - 1954-1957, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 28)
      - 1952-1954, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 29)
      - 1963-1966, 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - 1962-1963, 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - 1939-1948, 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - 1950, 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Geophysical Fluid Dynamics Laboratory, 1969; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - General Electric Company, 1962-1970; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - General Motors Corporation, 1955-1960; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Gilbert, Richard E, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Graduate School, 1941-1969; more than 13 folders
      - Actions of the Faculty Committee, 1946-1955; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Council, Griffin Breuer, 1956-1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Representatives - Committee on M.A Degree, 1955; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - Funds for Graduate Work, 1945; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - Seniors Enrolled in Graduate Courses, 1952; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - Alumni of the University, 1955-1962; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - Committee, 1949-1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1969; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence and Other, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 17)
      - Office, 1954-1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 18)
      - Vital Statistics, 1957-1961; 4 folders (Box 80, Folder 19 to 22)
      - Catalogue and Ideas - Revision Copy, 1954-1955; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 23)
      - Student Lists, 1941-1947; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Departmental Averages and Grades, 1961; 2 folders
      - Class of 1962, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Class of, 1961; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Graduate and Undergraduate Grades, 1959-1970; more than 21 folders
      - Spring Term, 1959-1970; more than 10 folders
        - 1966-1967, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 3)
          [restricted until 2042]
        - 1969-1970, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 4)
          [restricted until 2045]
        - 1968-1969, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 5)
          [restricted until 2044]
        - 1967-1968, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 6)
        - 1965-1966, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 7)
          [restricted until 2041]
        - 1963-1964, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 8)
          [restricted until 2039]
        - 1962-1963, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 9)
          [restricted until 2038]
        - 1961-1962, 2 folders (Box 81, Folder 10 to 11)
        - 1960-1961, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 12)
        - 1959-1960, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 13)
          [restricted until 2035]
      - Fall Term, 1959-1970; 11 folders
        - 1966-1967, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 14)
          [restricted until 2047]
        - 1959-1960, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 15)
        - 1969-1970, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 16)
        - 1968-1969, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 17)
        - 1967-1968, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 18)
        - 1965-1966, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 19)
        - 1964-1965, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 20)
          [restricted until 2040]
        - 1963-1964, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 21)
        - 1962-1963, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 22)
        - 1961-1962, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 23)
        - 1960-1961, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Graphics Department, 1951-1966; 4 folders
      - 1965-1966, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - 1951-1960, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - 1962-1963, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - 1961-1962, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Green, James L, 1962-1971; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Green, John C, Foundation, 1958-1959; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Grounds and Buildings, 1952-1963; 2 folders
      - Janitors, Duties, 1952; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Memoranda to Meyers, MacMillan, Quick, 1952-1963; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - 'G' Miscellaneous, 1950-1963; 8 folders
      - 1962-1963, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - 1960-1961, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - 1958-1960, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - 1958-1959, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - 1957-1958, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - 1956-1957, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - 1955-1956, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - 1950-1955, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Graduate School Enrollment in Engineering, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Graduate Degrees Granted for Fifth Year, 1924-1946; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Graduate Enrollment by Departments, 1945-1964; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Graduate Master of Arts Degree Awarded, 1950-1963; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Graduate Master of Science Degree Awarded, 1946-1963; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Graduate Doctor of Philosophy Degrees Awarded, 1948-1963; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Graduate Fellowships - Engineering Departments, 1961-1965; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Haas Otto Charitable Trust, 1960; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Haco Machinery Company, 1958; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - Hazeltine Corporation, 1953; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Harvard School of Business Administration, 1954-1957; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Harvard University, 1952-1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Heacock, Frank A., 1922-1961; 2 folders
      - 1949-1961, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 29)
      - 1922-1949, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - Higgins Fund, 1954; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 31)
    - Honor System in Princeton University, 1940-1955; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 32)
    - Hours of Instruction, 1945-1962; portions of 2 boxes
      - Spring Term, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 33)
      - Fall Term, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 34)
      - Fall Term, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 35)
      - Spring Term, 1958-1961; 4 boxes
        - 1960-1961, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 1)
        - 1959-1960, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 2)
        - 1958-1959, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Fall Term, 1958-1960; 2 folders
        - 1959-1960, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 4)
        - 1958-1959, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - 1957-1958, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - 1956-1957, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - 1951-1954, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - 1946-1948, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Report to Dean Brown, 1945-1955; 2 folders
        - 1954-1955, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 10)
        - 1945-1951, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Hughes Aircraft Company, 1961; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Hutton, John Lawrence - T Schriver and Company Incorporated, 1952-1960; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - 'H' Miscellaneous, 1952-1963; 7 folders
      - 1962-1963, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - 1960, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - 1956-1958, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - 1958-1961, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - 1956-1958, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - 1958-1959, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - 1952-1957, 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Industrial Reactor (Plainsboro), 1965-1970; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - In Term Work Study Program, circa 1950; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - International Business Machines Corp, 1951-1957; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - International Association for Exchange of Students, 1954-1957; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Introduction to Engineering, 1961; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 25)